Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part III WAG.025.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Departments, Chapters, and Divisions, 1940-2009
  - Subseries A: Anti-Discrimination Department, 1943-1969
    - New York State Commission Against Discrimination, 1948 (Box 279, Folder 33)
    - Ohio, 1948 (Box 279, Folder 34)
    - Oklahoma, 1948 (Box 279, Folder 35)
    - Package Programs, 1948 (Box 279, Folder 36)
    - Painters Union, 1948 (Box 279, Folder 37)
    - Pat, Jacob: "Story of the Jewish Labor Committee", 1948 (Box 279, Folder 38)
    - Pegler, Westbrook, 1948 (Box 279, Folder 39)
    - Philadelphia, PA, 1948 (Box 279, Folder 40)
    - Posters, 1948 (Box 279, Folder 41)
    - Post War World Council, 1948 (Box 279, Folder 42)
    - Presbyterian Institute of Industrial Relations, 1948 (Box 279, Folder 43)
    - President's Report on Civil Rights, 1948 (Box 279, Folder 44)
    - Radio Scripts, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Rand School, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Reports, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Reprint Orders, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Resolutions (Adopted), 1948 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Resolutions (Proposed), 1948 (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - "Role of Immigrants in the American Labor Movement", 1948 (Box 280, Folder 7)
    - "Rumor Clinic", 1948 (Box 280, Folder 8)
    - Salert, Irving, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 9)
    - Salert, Irving: Memos, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 10)
    - San Francisco, CA, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 11)
    - Schools and Institutes, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 12)
    - Shapiro, Elliot, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 13)
    - Socialist Party, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 14)
    - Socialists in the Trade Union Movement (United States), 1948 (Box 280, Folder 15)
    - Songs, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 16)
    - Speakers Bureau, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 17)
    - Staff Conference, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 18)
    - State Commission Against Discrimination, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 19)
    - Student League for Industrial Democracy, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 20)
    - Suall, Irwin, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 21)
    - Telegrams, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 22)
    - Textile Workers Union of America, Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO), 1948 (Box 280, Folder 23)
    - "To Secure These Rights", 1948 (Box 280, Folder 24)
    - Training Bureau for Jewish Communal Service, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 25)
    - Union Discrimination, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 26)
    - United Automobile Workers (UAW), 1948 (Box 280, Folder 27)
    - United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 28)
    - United Hebrew Trades, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 29)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 30)
    - United Textile Workers of America (UTW), American Federation of Labor (AFL), 1948 (Box 280, Folder 31)
    - University of Michigan, Workers Extension Service, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 32)
    - Washington, DC: Segregation, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 33)
    - Welfare Funds, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 34)
    - Wise, Stephen, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 35)
    - Women's Trade Union League, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 36)
    - Workers Defense League, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 37)
    - Workers Education Bureau of America, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 38)
    - Workmen's Circle, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 39)
    - Zimmerman, Charles, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 40)
    - Zimmerman, Charles: "Class Approach", 1948 (Box 280, Folder 41)
    - Zyvion, 1948 (Box 280, Folder 42)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1949 (Box 280, Folder 43)
    - American Association for a Democratic Germany, 1949 (Box 280, Folder 44)
    - American Bowling Congress, 1949 (Box 280, Folder 45)
    - American Council for Judaism, 1949 (Box 280, Folder 46)
    - American Council on Race Relations, 1949 (Box 280, Folder 47)
    - American Federation of Labor (AFL), 1949 (Box 280, Folder 48)
    - American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1949 (Box 280, Folder 49)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1949 (Box 280, Folder 50)
    - American Jewish Committee: Survey on Intercultural Education, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - American Jewish Congress: Commission on Law and Social Action (CLSA) Reports, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - American Jewish Labor Council, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - American Labor Education Service, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 6)
    - American Veterans Committee, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 7)
    - Anti-Defamation League, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 8)
    - Anti-Semitism, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 9)
    - Association of Jewish Community Relations Workers, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 10)
    - Boston: Civil Rights Week, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 11)
    - Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 12)
    - Cartoons, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 13)
    - Chicago Conference, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 14)
    - "Children's Album", 1949 (Box 281, Folder 15)
    - Churches of Christ, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 16)
    - Cincinnati, OH, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 17)
    - Citizens Committee on Displaced Persons, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 18)
    - City College, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 19)
    - City Liberties, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 20)
    - Civil Rights: General, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 21)
    - Cohen, Marjorie Merlin, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 22)
    - Committee against Jim Crow in Military Service and Training, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 23)
    - Committee to Combat Anti-Semitism, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 24)
    - Common Council for American Unity, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 25)
    - Communist Organizations (USA), 1949 (Box 281, Folder 26)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Boston, MA, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 27)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Brooklyn, NY, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 28)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Camden, NJ, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 29)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Cincinnati, OH, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 30)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Cleveland, OH, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 31)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Detroit, MI, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 32)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): General, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 33)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Houston, TX, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 34)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Indianapolis, IN, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 35)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Newark, NJ, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 36)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): New Haven, CT, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 37)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): St. Louis, MO, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 38)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Philadelphia, PA, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 39)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Pittsburgh, PA, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 40)
    - Confidential, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 41)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO), 1949 (Box 281, Folder 42)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO): Department of Education and Research, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 43)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO): Convention, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 44)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO): Convention resolutions, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 45)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO): Film Division, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 46)
    - Conventions, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 47)
    - Council for Equal Job Opportunity, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 48)
    - Council of Jewish Federations and Welfare Funds, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 49)
    - Counterattack, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 50)
    - Daily Worker, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 51)
    - Detroit, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 52)
    - Discussion Leaders Handbook, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 53)
    - Displaced Persons, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 54)
    - Educational Meeting, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 55)
    - Employment Bibliography, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 56)
    - Employment Discrimination, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 57)
    - Employment Service for Displaced Persons, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 58)
    - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1949 (Box 281, Folder 59)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC), 1949 (Box 282, Folder 1-2)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): Campaign Materials, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): Cleveland, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): Detroit, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 5)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): Illinois, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): Minnesota, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 7)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): National, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 8)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): National Council for, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 9)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): NY Council for, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 10)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): Philadelphia, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 11)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): References, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 12)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): State, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 13)
    - Field Offices, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 14)
    - Field Reports, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 15)
    - Films and Film Strips, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 16)
    - Finances, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 17)
    - Fisk University, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 18)
    - France (Children), 1949 (Box 282, Folder 19)
    - Georgia Workers Education Service, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 20)
    - Germany, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 21)
    - Goebel, Harry, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 22)
    - Housing, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 23)
    - Institute for Democratic Education, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 24)
    - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU), 1949 (Box 282, Folder 25)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), 1949 (Box 282, Folder 26)
    - International Labor Office, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 27)
    - International Solidarity Committee, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 28)
    - Israel, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 29)
    - Jacobs, Sam, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 30)
    - JLC/Anti-Defamation League (ADL): Joint Memorandums, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 31)
    - JLC/Anti-Defamation League (ADL): Relations, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 32)
    - JLC/AJC/Anti-Defamation League: National Policy and Program Committee, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 33)
    - JLC/AJC: National Labor Service, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 34)
    - JLC/AJC: Relations, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 35)
    - JLC: Cases, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 36)
    - JLC: Cleveland, OH, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 37)
    - JLC: Minneapolis, MN, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 38)
    - Jewish Occupational Council, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 39)
    - Jewish People's Fraternal Order, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 40)
    - Jewish Population Research, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 41)
    - Jewish Publication Society of America, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 42)
    - Jewish Survey Committee, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 43)
    - Jewish War Veterans, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 44)
    - Jewish Young Adult Council, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 45)
    - "Jews Behind the Iron Curtain", 1949 (Box 282, Folder 46)
    - Kaye, Betty (Betty Kaye Taylor), 1949 (Box 282, Folder 47)
    - Kentucky, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 48)
    - Labor and Civil Rights, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 49)
    - Labor Committee to Combat Intolerance: General, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 50)
    - Labor Conferences, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 51)
    - Labor Reports, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 52)
    - "Labor's Challenge" (Film), 1949 (Box 282, Folder 53)
    - Lapan, Martin, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 54)
    - Manual, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 55)
    - Maritime Union, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 56)
    - Mayor's Committee on Unity, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 57)
    - Memos: Field Staff, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 58)
    - Memos: Misc., 1949 (Box 282, Folder 59)
    - Michigan Labor Committee to Combat Intolerance, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 60)
    - Minnesota Jewish Council, 1949 (Box 282, Folder 61)
    - Muravchik, Emanuel, 1949 (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1949 (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - National Association of Intergroup Relations Officials, 1949 (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - National Committee for Fair Play in Bowling, 1949 (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC), 1949 (Box 283, Folder 5-7)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Ad Hoc Committee, 1949 (Box 283, Folder 8)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Class Approach, 1949 (Box 283, Folder 9)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Community Consultation, 1949 (Box 283, Folder 10)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Intercultural Education, 1949 (Box 283, Folder 11)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Inter-Faith Activities, 1949 (Box 283, Folder 12)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Overt Anti-Semitism, 1949 (Box 283, Folder 13)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Executive Committee, 1949 (Box 283, Folder 14-15)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Immigration Committee, 1949 (Box 283, Folder 16)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Joint Advisory Committee, 1949 (Box 283, Folder 17)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Legislative Information Committee, 1949 (Box 283, Folder 18)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Motion Picture Committee, Jan-Jun 1949 (Box 283, Folder 19)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Motion Picture Committee, Jul-Dec 1949 (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - National Conference on Christians and Jews, Inc., 1949 (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - National Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO) Committee to Abolish Discrimination, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 3)
    - National Emergency Civil Rights Mobilization, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - National Farm Labor Union, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 5)
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 6)
    - National Labor Service, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 7)
    - National Program Staff Meeting, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 8)
    - National Religion and Labor Foundation, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 9)
    - Negro Labor Committee, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 10)
    - New School for Social Research, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 11)
    - New York State Commission Against Discrimination, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 12)
    - New York State Committee on Discrimination in Housing, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 13)
    - Package Programs, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 14)
    - Pan-American Good Neighbor Forum, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 15)
    - Philadelphia, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 16)
    - Posters, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 17)
    - Post War World Council, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 18)
    - Prejudice Among Workers (C. Rose Proposed), 1949 (Box 284, Folder 19)
    - Presbyterian Institute of Industrial Relations, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 20)
    - Radio Programs, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 21)
    - Rand School, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 22)
    - Reisel, Victor, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 23)
    - Released Time in Education, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 24)
    - Religion and Public Schools, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 25)
    - Reports, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 26)
    - Reprint Orders, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 27)
    - Resolutions, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 28)
    - Role of Immigrants, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 29)
    - Roosevelt College: Report of Shop Practices Course, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 30)
    - "Rumor Clinic", 1949 (Box 284, Folder 31)
    - "Rumor Clinic:" Orders, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 32)
    - Saint Louis, MO, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 33)
    - Salert, Irving, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 34)
    - San Francisco, CA, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 35)
    - Schools and Institutes, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 36)
    - Shapiro, Elliott, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 37)
    - Silver, George, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 38)
    - Socialist Party, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 39)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 40)
    - Speeches, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 41)
    - State Commission Against Discrimination, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 42)
    - Stuyvesant Town, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 43)
    - Teachers Union, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 44)
    - Telegrams, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 45)
    - Textile Workers Union, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 46)
    - Training Bureau for Jewish Communal Services, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 47)
    - Trial Examinations at Labor Board (National), 1949 (Box 284, Folder 48)
    - United Automobile Workers (UAW), 1949 (Box 284, Folder 49)
    - United Housing Foundation, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 50)
    - United Service for New Americans, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 51)
    - United States Committee for Genocide Convention, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 52)
    - United States Student Assembly, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 53)
    - United Textile Workers, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 54)
    - West Side Committee on Civil Rights, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 55)
    - WEVD Radio, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 56)
    - Women's Division, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 57)
    - Women's Trade Union League, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 58)
    - Workers Defense League, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 59)
    - Workers Education Bureau, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 60)
    - Workmen's Circle: English-Speaking, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 61)
    - Workmen's Circle: Southern Region, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 62)
    - Zeidler, Frank, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 63)
    - Zimmerman, Charles, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 64)
    - Allocations, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 1)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 2)
    - American Bowling Congress, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 3)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 4)
    - American Council for Judaism, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 5)
    - American Council on Race Relations, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 6)
    - America Federation of Labor/Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Convention Resolutions, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 7)
    - American Federation of Labor (AFL), 1950 (Box 285, Folder 8)
    - American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1950 (Box 285, Folder 9)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 10)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 11)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 12)
    - American Labor Education Service, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 13)
    - American Labor Education Service: German Leadership Project, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 14)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 15)
    - Anti-Defamation League (ADL), 1950 (Box 285, Folder 16)
    - Anti-Defamation League (ADL): Field Work, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 17)
    - Anti-Defamation League (ADL): Joint Projects, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 18)
    - Anti-Defamation League (ADL): "Primer for Americans", 1950 (Box 285, Folder 19)
    - Anti-Discrimination Department: Reports, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 20)
    - Anti-Semitism (U.S.), 1950 (Box 285, Folder 21)
    - Association of Jewish Community Relations Workers, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 22)
    - Atlantic Union Committee, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 23)
    - Bell, Daniel, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 24)
    - "The Bigot in Our Midst:" Allport, Gordon, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 25)
    - Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 26)
    - Canada, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 27)
    - Catholic Statements, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 28)
    - Chanin, Herschell, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 29)
    - Chicago Industrial Union Council, Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO), 1950 (Box 285, Folder 30)
    - Citizens Committee on Displaced Persons, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 31)
    - Civil Rights, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 32)
    - "Civil Rights, Civil Liberties, and You", 1950 (Box 285, Folder 33)
    - Civil Rights Mobilization, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 34)
    - Commission on Law and Social Action, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 35)
    - Committee Against Jim Crow in Military Service, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 36)
    - "Committee of 100:" Groveland Four, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 37)
    - Committee of Employment Discrimination, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 38)
    - Committee on Federal Aid to Public Schools, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 39)
    - Committee on German Students, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 40)
    - Committee to Combat Anti-Semitism, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 41)
    - Common Council for American Unity, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 42)
    - Communism, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 43)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Boston, MA, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 44)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Brooklyn, NY, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 45)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Cleveland, OH, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 46)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Detroit, MI, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 47)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Houston, TX, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 48)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Indianapolis, IN, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 49)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Los Angeles, CA, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 50)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Minneapolis, MN, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 51)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): New Haven, CT, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 52)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Peoria, IL, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 53)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Pittsburgh, PA, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 54)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Portland, OR, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 55)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): St. Louis, MO, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 56)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Washington, DC, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 57)
    - Confidential, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 58)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO), 1950 (Box 285, Folder 59)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO): Committee to Abolish Discrimination, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 60)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO): Convention, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 61)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO): Department of Education and Research, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 62)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO): Resolutions, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 63)
    - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE), 1950 (Box 285, Folder 64)
    - Conventions, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 65)
    - Correspondence: General, 1950 (Box 285, Folder 66)
    - Council for Equal Job Opportunity, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Council of Jewish Federations, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 2)
    - Counterattack, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 3)
    - Displaced Persons, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 4)
    - Economic Cooperation Administration, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 5)
    - Education, Attack on, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 6)
    - Ellis, Pattie, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 7)
    - Employment Service for Displaced Persons, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 8)
    - Epstein, Melech, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 9)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC), 1950 (Box 286, Folder 10-11)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): Connecticut, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 12)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): Minnesota, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 13)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): Municipal, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 14)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): National, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 15)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): National Council for, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 16)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): New York Council for, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 17)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): Philadelphia, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 18)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): Rhode Island, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 19)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC): State, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 20)
    - Fair Practices Course, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 21)
    - Field Offices, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 22)
    - Field Reports, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 23)
    - Films, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 24)
    - Finances, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 25)
    - Fisk University, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 26)
    - Fleischman, Harry, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 27)
    - Free Trade Union Committee, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 28)
    - Genocide Convention, 1950 (Box 286, Folder 29)